Hello friends, I welcome you to
a new video today.  Friends, in today's video we are going to
talk
about PhonePe business.  Friends, if you also
use PhonePe business then watch this video till the
end.  Friends, in today's video we will
know
how loans are taken in PhonePe business in 2026.
Before starting the video, friends, if
you have not liked the video yet, then please
like the video.  So
friends, first of all let us open PhonePe business.
So now we have opened PhonePe business.
Friends, you might
also be seeing the screen on the side.  So friends, as soon as you
open PhonePe Business,
you will get to see the home screen like this.
So here you can see
friends, we have got a loan offer to see.
Friends, if you too have received a loan offer, then you will get to see it like this.
So friends, you can see here
what is written in the review details,
please complete loan review to available loan.
So here below is Resume, let
us click on this option now.  So friends, as soon as you
click, you can see here that
we have got a loan offer of Rs 73,000.
Friends, if we want to take a loan, then it has to be
completed in total four steps.
So here you can see now
friends, the first step is
complete KYC.  So you can see my KYC
is already complete and in the second one there is
review details.  Whatever basic details are there,
they will have to be entered and in the third one,
friends, it comes setup auto pay and
in the fourth one, friends, it is agreement.  So now first of all
friends,
we click on the continue option.  So friends, as soon as you click, you
can see here that the
loan is of Rs 73,000 and how much will the daily installment cost
us?  ₹241 daily installment will have to be paid
and friends, you
can see here that the loan is being applied for 12 months
and we will have to pay the total installment for 360 days,
which friends
can see here ₹73000 if the loan is offered,
friends, from which after deducting the processing fee of ₹345, it will
come to ₹69554,
friends, and friends, if we talk about the
loan interest, then you can see it here,
friends, in this way the interest rate is also
available to see, which is annual,
friends, its yearly interest is
18.62%,
friends, the interest is being charged for the year.
That is, if we talk about the total interest of Rs.
73000, then it is Rs. 13500 which is Rs. 68 which is going to be the
interest, friends, that is, the
total amount which we will have to return in 12 months is
Rs. 86578,
so now to take a loan, friends, simply click
here to see the basic details.
Click on the confirm option.
So friends, as soon as you click, the
next interface opens like this.
So this is the basic details in the review details
friends.  Now here we will
click on the confirm option.  So
friends, as soon as you click, you can see here that the
loan approval is
in process and you can see the review details, it is
completed.  Now in the third step
friends, it is on auto i.e. setup auto.  So
friends, as soon as you click on the Setup Auto Pay option, you can see here that the Phone
Pay option is coming and ₹2
is saying to pay here.  So now
from here we click on setup auto and from here we
setup it on auto.  Till then, if you have
not liked the video then
like the video friends.  Friends, you can see here that the
setup has also been completed on auto.
And the fourth step, friends, is the review
agreement.  That means friends, the company is giving the loan,
friends, an agreement paper will
come with it.  Friends, if you click here, you
can see here the meaning of agreement paper, you have got the
PDF to see, friends.  Only then
we will download the PDF from here.
Friends, what is there in it,
how much interest is being charged and for
how many days we have to pay the installment,
everything is written in the agreement paper,
friends.  After that,
friends, the box is visible below here.  Friends, after ticking this box,
click on Accept Agreement.  So you have to read it
friends.  Only after that you have to accept.
So
now we click on the Accept Agreement option.  So
after clicking, friends, please wait a little.   You
can see here that the option of continue is
coming.  Click on the continue option.
So friends, as soon as we click,
registration comes here.
So let's do the enterprise registration from here right now.
Friends, if you already have it then you will
also get to see the Udyam number here.
So friends, to do Udyam registration,
Simple asks for Aadhar number here.
Asks social category.  That means you will
enter which category it is and how many employees work.  You can
put anything here.  After that, if you submit it, you
can see that the
agreement enterprise registration has also been submitted here.
After that friends, as I continued, the
loan amount was showing here.  You
can see what is written below, friends, your
loan amount will be credited to your account
in seven working days.  That means seven working days
means friends that within seven working days
i.e. bank days, the
money will be credited to the account anytime within 7 days excluding Saturday and Sunday.
Now you have
seen friends how easily the
entire form was completed in four steps
and the loan also went into disbursement
friends.  Sometimes what happens is that in Disb it
shows seven days, sometimes it happens
that your
loan amount gets disbursed in half an hour, sometimes it takes 4
days, sometimes 5 days, sometimes 7 days,
friends.  So friends, we hope that you have
completely understood about PhonePe Business Loan.
Friends, if you liked the video even a little bit then like the video.
And friends, whatever doubt you have in your mind,
you can ask by commenting.  If you have
come to the channel for the first time, friends,
go down and subscribe to the channel.
See you again with a new video.  Till then
Jai Hind.